<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Horoscope 2015</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="desclaim">Disclaimer:</string>
    <string name="desclaim_text">Predications may vary from person to person Its a general prediction, for specific prediction about you, kindly the fill Enquiry Form.</string>
    <string name="exit_now">Exit Now</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="rate_this_app">Rate this app</string>
   
    <string name="rate_us">Rate Us</string>
    <string name="tell_a_friend">Tell a friend</string>
    <string name="about_us">About us</string>
    <string name="more_apps">More apps</string>
    <string name="disclaimer2">Disclaimer</string>
    <string name="aquarius">Aquarius\n(20Jan-18Feb)</string>
    <string name="aries">Aries\n(21Mar-19Apr)</string>
    <string name="cancer">Cancer\n(21Jun-22Jul)</string>
    <string name="capricorn">Capricorn\n(22Dec-19Jan)</string>
    <string name="gemini">Gemini\n(21May-20Jun)</string>
    <string name="leo">Leo\n(23Jul-22Aug)</string>
    <string name="libra">Libra\n(23Sept-22Oct)</string>
    <string name="pisces">Pisces\n(19Feb-20Mar)</string>
    <string name="sagittarus">Sagittarius\n(22Nov-21Dec)</string>
    <string name="scorpio">Scorpio\n(23Oct-21Nov)</string>
    <string name="taurus">Taurus\n(20April-20May)</string>
    <string name="virgo">Virgo\n(23Aug- 22Sep)</string>
    <string name="aquarius_monthly">Aquarius</string>
    <string name="aries_monthly">Aries</string>
    <string name="cancer_monthly">Cancer</string>
    <string name="capricorn_monthly">Capricorn</string>
    <string name="gemini_monthly">Gemini</string>
    <string name="leo_monthly">Leo</string>
    <string name="libra_monthly">Libra</string>
    <string name="pisces_monthly">Pisces</string>
    <string name="sagittarius_monthly">Sagittarius</string>
    <string name="scorpio_monthly">Scorpio</string>
    <string name="taurus_monthly">Taurus</string>
    <string name="virgo_monthly">Virgo</string>
    <string name="jan">Jan</string>
    <string name="feb">Feb</string>
    <string name="mar">Mar</string>
    <string name="apr">Apr</string>
    <string name="may">May</string>
    <string name="jun">Jun</string>
    <string name="july">Jul</string>
    <string name="aug">Aug</string>
    <string name="sep">Sep</string>
    <string name="oct">Oct</string>
    <string name="nov">Nov</string>
    <string name="dec">Dec</string>
    <string name="aquaris_apr">This month is good from the professional point of view as well from the family point of view. You will get happiness and you will be surrounded by many females.</string>
    <string name="aquaris_aug">For the married ones this is little disturbing as married life will have little problems and misunderstandings, but profession and family will do extremely well. Emotional involvement in all family issues will be there. Love in family at high pace.</string>
    <string name="aquarius_dec">Month of December is good for you. The coordination between you and spouse will be good. Profession will rise, partners will be helpful. All planning will be successful. The only negative parts of this is excessively fast in driving which can lead to accident.</string>
    <string name="aquarius_feb">This month is different for you during this month. You will enjoy as well as earn good amount of money but in the second half of the month you are over imaginative nature may make you depressive or some fears might developed.</string>
    <string name="aquarius_jan">Avoid loosing temperament. Your sort temper nature may spoil the show. Avoid saying no on the face. Avoid landing money especially to the friends or relatives.</string>
    <string name="aquarius_jul">This month is good for bachelors of marriageable age those who are married their married life is good. Your children will perform extremely well. Your family and social involvements will be on right track.</string>
    <string name="aquarius_jun">Avoid taking rash decisions this can lead to excessive expenses and hardship. Avoid spending money on friends otherwise family dispute might be there. Doing good in profession if take care of over expenses and unnecessary travels.</string>
    <string name="aquarius_mar">The month of March is good. You gain of confidence is there. At the same time your calculations and friendship is going to increase. In the second half of the month disputes with some relatives is indicated.</string>
    <string name="aquarius_may">This month will be little trouble some in family and financial matter but busyness in business will be there. Due to excessive involvements chances of hidden losses may be there.</string>
    <string name="aquarius_nov">This month is good for you. Except the fears good support from the father, from the wife, from the profession, everything will good. But at the same time some fears may be there. Avoid taking decisions in dark.</string>
    <string name="aquarius_oct">Month of October is little disturbing and different. In the first half you will see both ends of life the happiest and sorrow. In the first half married life will be hell. But in the second half you will get just opposite result. Father will favour you. Profession will sine in everything will be on right track.</string>
    <string name="aquarius_sept">Your spouse will prove to superior than you. At the same time your most of calculations will go wrong. But your emotions with the kids will be there. Unnecessary expenses will not be there.</string>
    <string name="aries_apr">For Ariens this month is mixed result giving. First half is full of romance, love and friendship. In second half focus only business will be there. Some business journey will be fruitful and that leads to good results. Avoid night driving in the second half of April.</string>
    <string name="aries_august">This month will create lots of ups &amp; downs or losses in profession. All profession decisions should be taken with caution. Family environment will also be tensed. If you are in joint family than visiting to the religious place is highly beneficial. If there is any disease that can aggravate some take the prevention.</string>
    <string name="aries_dec">December month is month of positive relations with spouse and mother. But the children will do better. In some of cases father’s health might create some problems. Emotionally you will get everything. Travels will be materialized.</string>
    <string name="aries_feb">During first half of February you will be troubled by enemies, misunderstandings or disputes may rise. But within the family peace will be there. Avoid unnecessary arguments, disputes. In second half chances of mishapping are there. Be attentive and careful while driving. A religious trip with mother will ward of they negative results.</string>
    <string name="aries_jan">In January 2015 your desires will come true, longed distance religious journey is indicated, relationship with the mother will be good and other family members will also grow. In second half of the month avoid taking rash and bold decisions. These decisions can lead to professional blunders, minor fight or disputes in professional are there. Those who are doing professional related to fire or force will see the positive trend. Lacerative income is also indicated.</string>
    <string name="aries_july">Celebration in the family can be there. Family friends will be happy and good. Some benefits from younger brother or partner can be aspected. Whatever suggestions you will give turn to be right for the others.</string>
    <string name="aries_jun">This month is little depressive on family and professional matters. Due to rough language you will face problems. Your mother might be hospitalized will face some long term disease. Careing mother will give excessively good result. If any surgery of eyes of your mother is pending than planned a surgery according. Even traveling abroad will not give good results.</string>
    <string name="aries_mar">March 2015 is little difficult month for the Ariens, expenses will be on the pick, unrecoverable losses are there. Avoid relationship with opposite sex. Chances of indulging into physical relation are on the higher side. If any court case or disputes are start that will aggravate for long.</string>
    <string name="aries_may">This month is like rollercoaster most of the time you will loose your temperament and after that you will be emotional. In first half the decision taken on professional and personal front will be result oriented. But in the second half some emotional setbacks can be there. In this month avoid expressing everything to even close once.</string>
    <string name="aries_nov">This month is very problematic for you. This can lead you to bad name and problem some in business. Your younger sister can create little problems for you. Kids will go out of control. If in partnership avoid taking risk. If some dispute rises than opt for compromise.</string>
    <string name="aries_oct">Your father may suffer from poor health or some bad name. If there is some litigation they will loose the betel. Business losses are also aspected due to that some family problem may rise. Your kids will be attractive towards opposite sex and chances of getting involved are on the higher side.</string>
    <string name="aries_sep">This month is full of expenses and wasteful travel during this month all your calculation will go wrong. At the same time get some good news from beloved once or children is there. Avoid any disputes with your mother or mother-in-law.</string>
    <string name="cancer_apr">This is the best month of year. You will have emotional support. Your professional will touch the new heights. Parents and family will be very happy with you. If you are suffering from some diseases you will come out of crunch of disease. Avoid doing anything unfair because everything will come to you without putting much effort. Association of opposite sex at the place of profession will be there and will remain happy in their association.</string>
    <string name="cancer_aug">This month is full of discipline in personal life. You will try to complete all your commitments. Due to excessive commitments your profession may suffer. Due to excessive projects or work load you might face some professional disappointments. Your excessive discipline towards yourself and others will be relaxed in the second half of the month.</string>
    <string name="cancer_dec">Last month of the year is also not good. This might spoil peace of mind during the first half your family relationship may not be very good. You may face criticism or some mysterious situations. In the last face of the month misunderstandings in the business or family matter is also indicated. Health of your father may be problematic. If he is facing any skin problems than treat it immediate. Loosing temperament might affect your work efficiency will make you controversial.</string>
    <string name="cancer_feb">In month of February your all religious activities will dominate and family environment may be affected due to these activities. Your emotional bent of mind towards the excessive activities might lead to some professional disturbance also. Your kids might not perform well and your married life will be highly affected. Avoid going to religious journeys in groups. If your wife is having some gynecological disorders get them treated earliest. This can be dangerous.</string>
    <string name="cancer_jan">Take your health on guard because health problems may be there. Due to excessive health burden, stress or some stress related problems may be there. But in totality your wife will help you to sort out your personal &amp; emotional issues. Professional activities will be average, but the chances of accidents are there. In the second half avoid fast driving or some emotional communication with the strangers.</string>
    <string name="cancer_jul">July month is full of disappointment. Everything will be irregular and irrational. Lose of peace of mind will be there. Due to irrational decision your family may be annoyed but in the second half of the month you will rectify your all mistakes. Your communication gape between the family members will be minimized. Avoid excessive calculations or loosing temperament. This may affect you very badly.</string>
    <string name="cancer_jun">This month is full of confusions and indecisive, practical &amp; emotional imbalance can lead to some dangerous situation. In the first half happiness is associated with the little struggle but second half is little disappointing. If you are in relationship chances of loosing relationship are there.</string>
    <string name="cancer_mar">In the month of March fate will smile on you, things will turn desirous. If you suffering from joints pain than take care of yourself. Otherwise this month is for creating new partnership, starting of new venture. If anyone in family specially younger or elder brothers settled in abroad avoid disputes with them if any misunderstanding will develop than clear this at the earliest. Visiting to a religious place with spouse or spending some time with spouse will be highly beneficial.</string>
    <string name="cancer_may">This month will be mixture of ups &amp; downs, happiness &amp; sadness during the first half you will enjoy all luxurious, comforts, full control of your life, you will remain happy. Things will turn in your tune. But in the second half some bad news from kids can spoil the sprite of first half.  But you will regularly helping the needy.</string>
    <string name="cancer_nov">This month is quite promising intern of happiness, financial gains and family environment. Everyone in the family will be cooperative and keep their interest family affair. Second part of the month might be little critical, financial stress is there. Misunderstanding with the kids will prove to be fetal.</string>
    <string name="cancer_oct">During this month you will keep all your commitments even at the cause of your own lose. Your invested money may not work. If you have promised something to your younger brothers or sisters this can lead to you bad name. Eating and stream spicy &amp; sweet can give you emotional instability. Traveling in the second part of the month is there.</string>
    <string name="cancer_sep">This month is very much promising for the native. This will give you desires result name, fame, prosperity and enjoyment all together. In this month you will rip the fruit of happiness, love and romance. Your desires will be fulfilled and dreams will come true. You will enjoy most of the month during the last part of the month. Differences with the father can not be ruled out.</string>
    <string name="capricorn_apr">This month is little depressive, some family problems may be there. Avoid a traveling in the joint family. If you are having younger brothers/sisters avoid excessive conversation with them. If you are young then in mid twenties and affair can be there.</string>
    <string name="capricorn_aug">Try to control your temper otherwise you will be looser. Disputes with their spouse during the whole month will possible, at the same time you are excessive busyness may create some problems. If you are having partnership, avoid all types of disputes. You may get deceived in love in second half of the month. If you obese then take care of your liver.</string>
    <string name="capricorn_dec">Little mistake in professional issues may cost you very high. Avoid association or excessive dealing with the opposite sex otherwise you will be very calculative. Avoid arguments with your elders.</string>
    <string name="capricorn_feb">This month is good for taking bold decisions, family happiness, gains this might going to create all positive results. Due to aggressive decisions sudden rise is expected. Avoid eating excessive fast food or conversation with opposite sex. This only can lead to controversies.</string>
    <string name="capricorn_jan">This month is good as you will get. It give you good results, married life will be good. If you are female then extra ordinary happiness from husband is there. Avoid using abusing language this can create some misunderstandings and family problems. Avoid going excessively to religious place.</string>
    <string name="capricorn_jul">This is an average month. You might suffer from health point of view but at the same time your partner will be supportive. Your younger brothers may create some disputes. Father may become against you but a close friend will rescue you from all controversies and allegations.</string>
    <string name="capricorn_jun">If you are in marriageable age then chances of marriege on the higher side otherwise you will have good marital happiness. Kids will perform very well. You will feel blessed to have these kids. Chances of getting multiple incomes are on the higher side.</string>
    <string name="capricorn_mar">This month is full of calculation and these calculations come to be true and results can be seen. Avoid excessive traveling this can lead to some negative results. If you are having partners they will give full cooperation. Married life will be good. If this chart is of female chances of getting married are on the higher side.</string>
    <string name="capricorn_may">This month is full of ups &amp; downs. You will travel a lot but remain disturb from the opposite sex. Some arguments in the family might be there. Health of the father may be spoiled.</string>
    <string name="capricorn_nov">Professionally this month is average. You are decision taken will be on the right track. You will have good reputation in your profession. Avoid investing money in this month. The money invested or given for loan may get spoiled. Avoid any religious controversies or religious difference of opinion. Your family life will be good.</string>
    <string name="capricorn_oct">This month is full of aggressive, disputes and problems. You might face allegations. Your investment may go on the wrong track. Difference of opinion with father or with some government officers can not be ruled out. Avoid traveling for business purpose. If you develop some abdominal problems then get it is immediate checked.</string>
    <string name="capricorn_sep">This is hilarious for you. Complete enjoyment and full of fun and entertainment you will get association with opposite sex. Avoid foreign travel for fun, chances of bad health in abroad are there.</string>
    <string name="gemini_apr">Taking blind decision can create major problems or loss of reputation. Avoid any disputes with the government or with the government officers. Continuous and dedicated working is the key to success. During the month you might get circulars money in saving for future will give you extra ordinary results. Avoid spending money emotionally on your kids.</string>
    <string name="gemini_aug">Harsh speech can be problematic for you. During the month number of situation may compel you to become harsh. But you will loose finances as well as peace of mind. If you having any joint venture with the younger brothers or with the same age group you must take care of relationship or profession both. Avoid taking excessive hot food can cause liver problems.</string>
    <string name="gemini_dec">The last of month of year is full of disappointment and problems might going to face family disputes, emotional, social and professional problems. Your health might not support you. You will feel frustrated but at the same time lose of peace of mind will add fuel into the fire. Difference of opinion with everybody is the routine. In the second half you may face trouble some married life.</string>
    <string name="gemini_feb">The fate will smile on you can accumulate lot of money with the help of your sharp decisions. But little carelessness approach towards the family might give you little disturbance. If there is some disputes with the aunty or sister than avoid stretching the disputes just finished it and be decisive. Avoid doing any mall practice.</string>
    <string name="gemini_jan">Some financial disputes may leads to bad name or some disturbance. Avoid taking any guarantee or responsibilities. Due to others chances of bad name can not be ruled out. If you are suffering from any court case that might gives you bad results. Due to careless approach towards the family will give negative results. Some health problems to the female members of the family can not be ruled out. Visiting to the Goddess Maa Durga temple will be highly beneficial.</string>
    <string name="gemini_jul">This month is action packed, all around happiness, growth will be there. You will be extra ordinary active for all parts of life. Decision making will be sharp. Performance some religious function at home will give good results. The whole month will be positive. All desires and hopes will be fulfilled. Relationship with the father, mother &amp; co-borns will be good. Investing in Gold will be highly beneficial.</string>
    <string name="gemini_jun">June will be regular month for the native, mixture of joy and happiness. In the first part of the month loss of confidence, problems, disputes may be there but in the second part of the month all around happiness, gains and favorable situations will knock the doors. In the second half happiness &amp; money both the increase but your selective behaviour may give negative approach. Helping the poor or needy will be highly beneficial for the growth. The females will suffer due to some emotional crunches.</string>
    <string name="gemini_mar">This month is very good for professional and emotional gains. Accumulation of money will be there. Increase the name &amp; fame and family happiness will be there. For some short span of time you might have to leave away from the family. Avoid working for long hours or late night. Giving some sweets to the young girls will be highly beneficial for the native. Helping some old male or visiting to some religious place with father will give extra ordinary good results.</string>
    <string name="gemini_may">This month is mixed result giving. First have will be commanding, progressive lot of profitability will be there. Avoid working emotionally. But in the second half you will be exert. You are physical and emotional energy level will come down. Avoid thinking excessively and traveling abroad might not give you happiness.</string>
    <string name="gemini_nov">This month is little critical in all aspects of life. Family problems and professional disputes might come in way. Chances of bad name from kids may be there. You will do maximum for the family but certain misunderstandings can lead to lose of reputation as well lose of monetary gains. Take care of your health, poor health and multiple pains can create bad results.</string>
    <string name="gemini_oct">This month will be an average and very dull month. During the month you may face lot of problems and odd situations. Your close ones might create some disturbances. If you are having younger brothers or partners or younger of your age this can cause multiple disputes and some misunderstandings. In the second half of the month your father’s health may be problematic. During the whole month some family responsibilities will be there. Your health and stamina will stand with you. Avoid any arguments.</string>
    <string name="gemini_sep">Avoid being mean minded. This can result into family dispute otherwise religious travel, happiness will be there. During the first half of the month father will favour you. You will be supported by your friends but during the second half differences with your parents can not be ruled out. If you are traveling abroad than avoid traveling with the family but business trip will be suitable.</string>
    <string name="leo_apr">Stress will be reduce but the expenses will remain same, family tension will be on higher side. If you are having partnership within your family this partnership will be affected. Short travel is good but some business issues might be going to disturb. If you are having partnership with opposite sex that will be highly beneficial.</string>
    <string name="leo_aug">This is month is again mixture of many things religion, romance &amp; business. Avoid mixing the drinking and driving this could lead to some major setbacks. This month will be little stressful, if you use excessive electronics than avoid using it. This can lend you in soup. But continuous religious activities will ward of the negative results.</string>
    <string name="leo_dec">Last month of this year is full of controversies, problems and odd situations. Over expression may spoil the family environment. If anything is controversial than avoid. Avoid taking part in arguments, discussions otherwise you will be blamed for something wrong. If you having good friends then avoid excessive intoxicants or traveling abroad with the friends can be dangerous. Control on your speech is the key of success.</string>
    <string name="leo_feb">February is a different month. Someone of opposite sex will become suddenly close to you and you develop some intimate relationships with the person. This may leads to multiple problems and expenses. If you having friends who take excessive intoxicants. Avoid excessive interaction with them. If you are found of drinking than avoid this it can lead to losses. In the second half of the month keeps silence otherwise some different complications might come.</string>
    <string name="leo_jan">In the month of January you will face some minor accidents, bad name or problems from some close friends or relatives. Family environment will be little troublesome. At the same time your expenses on the pick. The second half is little disturbing from the family point of view, you might face some issues and objections in family affairs.</string>
    <string name="leo_jul">This month is mixture of everything love, romance, happiness and all positive news. Business will grow. Expenses will be under control, if you have any planning for the business growth. This month is favourable for graving the growth opportunity. Your relationship with spouse is good. In the second half of this month you should take care of all legal hassles.</string>
    <string name="leo_jun">The pace of progress will continue business growth, emotional and family satisfaction on the higher level. Rising trend towards the business will be there, family will continuously like you will enjoy continuously family happiness and travels. Spending with caution is recommended.</string>
    <string name="leo_mar">Due to the previous month chances of disputes are there. Some bad name or allegations might be troubling your emotional and professional pace. Avoid exploiting relationship or close friends. Excessive exertion may leads to fatigue. Your spouse may develop some problems relating to bones or skin.</string>
    <string name="leo_may">During the month of May business will be on great guns. Expansion will be good. Everything will be in favour. Avoid rash driving this can be to some minor accidents but on the whole divine blessings, family happiness, growth in business and good relationship with the kids are there. Avoid gambling in this month, if you are found of gambling.</string>
    <string name="leo_nov">This month will be full of expressions, religious activities, emotional balance is there. Friend’s circles is going to increase. Avoid excessive involvement in your friends and roaming around. If you are having younger brother take care your relationship with the younger ones. Indulging into the religious activities will give you highly benefic results.</string>
    <string name="leo_oct">This month is like sweet and sour together. First phase will be full of expenses and bad name but in the second phase you will get the desires results. Tight the screw of your kids. If you are in education then be prepare for different results. In the second half only continuous efforts will be result oriented.</string>
    <string name="leo_sep">"This month is again very good for you will give you name, fame and all around prosperity. If you are married than avoid extra relationship. If in love avoid flirting others than multiple growths in business indicated. If some works related to Govt is pending than just finish it at the earliest possible because this opportunity is good. "</string>
    <string name="libra_apr">This month is bad for the females of the family. If your mother is suffering from some disease the disease will take bad shape. Your wife will also be affected. If you are having daughter she might also be in problems. The planetary combination shows you will be broken due to family problems or diseases.</string>
    <string name="libra_aug">This month is extremely good for you. Your business will take new heights. If your planning to takes some bold decisions that will be fruitful. Do not hide whatever comes in your mind. If your planning for exports then persue it seriously.</string>
    <string name="libra_dec">This month is a very different result giving full of romance, wrong decisions, allegations and some of your bad habits may come up. Do not take bold and blind decisions. Emotional stress will be there due to others. In general in this year you will feel frustrated and helpless.</string>
    <string name="libra_feb">Month of February will be full of expenses and travels. If you are planning to go abroad then you can plan it. Your all desires relating to the foreign will be fulfilled. At the same time your kids may be spoiled and due to that you may remain tensed.</string>
    <string name="libra_jan">In January avoid any wrong commitments or any arguments with your kids. This can lead to some disputes with them. In the complete month avoid taking non-veg or drinks this will affect your professional as well as personal life.</string>
    <string name="libra_jul">This month is good. Your professional recognition will be there. You will complete your family expectation but your mother may remain irritated or suffer from some painful disease.</string>
    <string name="libra_jun">Everything will remain settled if you drink and drive then the month will be dangerous and difficult for you. If your father having tendencies to drive avoid driving ask him to take the driver. If your wife is in business then avoid taking collective decisions</string>
    <string name="libra_mar">Month of March is little disturbing from the female side if you having business regarding cosmetics or fashion industry then avoid taking rash decisions because your wrong decisions may create unnecessarily issues in your professional life. Health of your mother may be little problematic some undiagnosable problems to the mother can be there.</string>
    <string name="libra_may">In this month you have little good results with regard to family profession. If your planning for the short distance travel then execute it at the earliest possible. If some matters regarding to the government are still pending then in this month you can sort out the same.</string>
    <string name="libra_nov">Everything will be under control except your expenses. Keep a watch on your expenses. If this remain under control everything will be stable otherwise situation can hamper your confidence.</string>
    <string name="libra_oct">All around growth and success will be there. Whatever your planning that will be successful. If working for foreign countries then increase as much as you can. Your calculation will be perfectly alright. Your business, family all activities will be good.</string>
    <string name="libra_sep">Planned exports can create wonders and will be highly beneficial. You will be recognize very short time. Family happiness, growth and everything will be good. If you are having excessive junk in your house then remove that. This will effect the profession as well as your romantic life.</string>
    <string name="pisces_apr">First half of April is good for confidence, promotion will be there. Kids will be happy at the same time will visit to some religious place. Short journeys will be full of enjoyments if you have younger sister then you will get the great help.</string>
    <string name="pisces_aug">This month is little troublesome may face financial losses or disputes. Short journeys are indicated but on other hand your kids will shine well. Visiting to Goddess Maa Durga temple will ward of the negativity.</string>
    <string name="pisces_dec">The last month the year is little problematic. Difference of opinion with father or spouse will be there. Some secretive losses will be there. They will be problems might knock, bad name and reputation might be there. The only positive thing will come during the second phase of the month that is some good or new business opportunity.</string>
    <string name="pisces_feb">This month of full of enjoyment, relationship with opposite sex can not be ruled out. Difference with own spouse can be there. Kids will perform well there. All around happiness will prevail.</string>
    <string name="pisces_jan">This month is good for kids. Desires will come true, rise in profession is there. At the same time fate will favour. Some misunderstanding with the spouse will be the routine matter of the year.</string>
    <string name="pisces_jul">In July emotional troubleness is due to blind decisions. Avoid indulging in others matters. Doing religious activities will give you good results. If any dispute comes in the family try to sort out by seating together.</string>
    <string name="pisces_jun">Month of June is good. All desires will be fulfilled. Fate will continue to give good results. You just need to control your irritation. Success will follow you. If you are planning to go for a long journey then that will remain pending.</string>
    <string name="pisces_mar">This month is entirely different for you. Sometime you will be romantic sometime irritating and sometime sort temper. But you professional achievement will be good. If anything relating to the govt. is pending keep this pending for 2 or 4 months it will be getting done automatically.</string>
    <string name="pisces_may">If you are in business take care of your ups &amp; downs. Avoid getting irritating and minor issues. If you have younger sister or young daughter they will be lucky during this month.</string>
    <string name="pisces_nov">This month is full of fun, enjoyments and positive results. If you married your marital happiness will be on the pick. If you are in love your beloved one will give you extremely caring and romance will be there. Avoid excessive eating during dating. Avoid dating married person this can lead to loss of image.</string>
    <string name="pisces_sep">This month is good. Support of parents will be there but as a routine of year difference with spouse will be there. Avoid landing money to someone. If you are young falling in love or making some new friends will be frequent. Avoid eating excessively this can lead to the liver problems.</string>
    <string name="pisces_oct">In this month some different with the father might come out due to that emotional disturbance is there. Avoid all types of clashes professional or financially. Emotional stress wills sake you now one will come to support you.</string>
    <string name="sagittarius_apr">This month will disappoint you. You may have wasteful expenses, losses or some disputes. Your wife may not keep herself healthy some problems may be there. But your kids will perform well during the month.</string>
    <string name="sag_aug">Drive with passion, loosing your peace of mind can be dangerous. Minor accident is indicated during the month. Avoid traveling with the complete family. Some family members might spark some tensions during the travel especially at the religious visits.</string>
    <string name="sag_dec">This month will be good your all plannings, calculations will come true. You will get the professional benefits as well as family bond will be stronger. Avoid excessive control on situation almost month is good for you.</string>
    <string name="sag_feb">Take care your profession in the month of February your professional seriousness is required. Because due to some known serious issues you may be affected professionally, if you working with the younger brothers or young partners then avoid harsh speech with them.</string>
    <string name="sag_jan">This month is just an average. First half the month will be commanding but in the second half your money might struck off somewhere. Avoid landing money even to close friends or to the relatives. Little arguments in the family might be there.</string>
    <string name="sag_jul">If you will take precaution this month will be good otherwise little controversial. Chances of getting family disputes are on the higher side. That can lead to the bad name as well loss of peace of mind. If you will keep passions your family will remain intact otherwise you may develop some family problems also.</string>
    <string name="sag_jun">If you wasted money on your affairs that will come in light. In month of June some controversies may rise. This might come to know to your family and your reputation may be on the stack. If your wife is on the healthier side take care of her because chances of poor health or disputes with the spouse can not be ruled out.</string>
    <string name="sag_mar">Some family function might give you soothing results. But at the same time your professional in decisiveness might trouble you. If there is any disputes during the family function then sort out this with passions. Loss of passions means loss of reputation.</string>
    <string name="sag_may">This month is little better than March and April. You will be emotionally uplifted will keep positive approach. Your kids will be helpful. If you are in love that love is in converted in to marriage. Avoid spending money in your love affairs.</string>
    <string name="sag_nov">This month is little problematic you might face some difference of opinion with partners in business. Loss of reputation is there. But at the same time expenses will remain under control.</string>
    <string name="sag_oct">Avoid taking blind decisions this can give major loss might be loss of reputation. If you are with father difference of opinion with father may be there. Avoid remaining in stress become stress will condition might lead to depression.</string>
    <string name="sag_sep">This month is good. If you are pursuing for some professional activities that will come true. If you are planning to visit some religious place that to prove to be good. At the same time your expense will remain in control and family environment will be soothing.</string>
    <string name="scorpio_apr">Some good news in the family may be there. If you are of marriageable age you might get married. If you have any disputes with the wife or in married life that can be sorted out. Your kids will bring name &amp; fame but tape your laziness.</string>
    <string name="scorpio_aug">Professionally or emotionally August month is good. Professional desires will come true, chances of developing new sources is on the higher side. Emotional marital relationship will be good. At the same time chances of getting hidden wealth or sudden profit can not be ruled out.</string>
    <string name="scorpio_dec">Little controversial month is there. You might going to face very odd situations in business, in family and in friends also. Due to your carelessness you may be in tight corner. Avoid taking risk or any controversial decisions.</string>
    <string name="scorpio_feb">Delays and negative thoughts may land you in little depression. But your religious activities will continue as usual. Short term professional terms are there. Due to excessive busyness family environment may be tensed but in routine all the work will be executed.</string>
    <string name="scorpio_jan">This month is good for spiritual achievements. At the same time you might delay your routine work due to your religious works. Over involvement in religion might lead to some family differences. If you are married and having a sister at home disputes between your spouse and sister may be there month will be in routine.</string>
    <string name="scorpio_jul">From the health point of view July is little poor. Health problems especially allergic disorders may be there. If you have tendency of major body ache can be there. Migraine or sudden minor accidents may be there. Due to over exertion you might face physical and emotional stress.</string>
    <string name="scorpio_jun">June is the most dangerous month of the year. In this month you will be lazy, controversial, emotional or might land up into emotional clutches but you are spiritual progress will be continue. Your own family members may criticize you in front of others. Due to that you may have little bad reputation.</string>
    <string name="scorpio_mar">This month will be slow but full of move sense at the same time little worries from kids might be there. You keep birds eye view on the kids if you have sister is marriageable age the chances of fixing her alliance are there. If your son is working then his hardwork will proves to be good. Your all emotional desires will come true.</string>
    <string name="scorpio_may">Whatever you think that will comes true little difference your spouse may be there. She might suffer from gynecological disorders at the same time your kids might little abusive for you. Your professional and spiritual achievements will be on track.</string>
    <string name="scorpio_nov">November month is full of complication of desires as well of business growth, family will be good. If you want to start some new profession or want to develop some new source of income it is good for this. If you have some engagements in abroad that will be successful.</string>
    <string name="scorpio_oct">Again this month is good for profession as well as for the family meters. Little laziness can spoil the show but overall you will get very good results. Your professional activities will be good. Chances of some losses from the government are indicated.</string>
    <string name="scorpio_sep">Action packed month is waiting for you to gaze your performance. You will have kind of satisfaction. Your kids will do well. Your hold in professional life is going to increase you will perform the best. Emotional and social relationship will be good.</string>
    <string name="taurus_apr">This month is a very different month for you. Luxurious, comforts and lot of expenditure is waiting for you intern. If you are in love or relationship this is going to more closer help or benefit from younger brothers will give you very beneficial results. If you are married than avoid physical relations with the other partner, otherwise bad effects will go to kids. In the second half of this month your expectation and calculation will go on wrong track. Do not get upset you just need focus on your profession you can’t this difficulty.</string>
    <string name="taurus_aug">This month is full of expenses and travel. Avoid expenses which can be avoidable. Some major misunderstandings with younger brother or brother-in-law can be there. A religious family function can help you to coming out of mess. Traveling with the mother will be beneficial.</string>
    <string name="taurus_dec">This month is not good. Father’s health may be poor. Your spouse may also face some health issues. You may remain irritated during the complete month. Your kids will be against you. If you have business in partnership the chances of separation can not be ruled out. Dealing all professional or emotional factors consciously will be helpful.</string>
    <string name="taurus_feb">February months is average for you. You may face opposition from spouse or some business partners. In your family emotional stress will be increase. In the first half of January chances of involvement in extra marital relations or love at work place is indicated. In the second half kids may create some occurred situation to you. Chances of getting depressed are on the higher site. Due to some wrong decision your income may affected.</string>
    <string name="taurus_jan">In January 2015 your professional travels will be going to increase due to excessive travels fatigue will be there. Starting of new venture can not be ruled out. But at the same time your father may fall ill or you may have some disputes with your father. In the second half your father will recover but your professional travel will remain the same and your decision making will be very sharp. If you are blessed with your sister than giving some gift in shape of cloth or sweets will be extra ordinary result giving.</string>
    <string name="taurus_jul">In July professional troubleness may not you. Interference of opposite sex especially some female may off track your profession. Try to control on your food habits and speech both. A regular food habits and high speech can lead to depressive environment also.</string>
    <string name="taurus_jun">Excessive heat in temperament will be continued in this month. It is going to create worst family environment. Your kids will away from you and you are deprived of your partners love. If this behaviour continuous your kids will start opposing you. Visiting a religious place with the mother/mother-in-law will be very helpful to you. In second half of this month complete control on your speech and temperament is required.</string>
    <string name="taurus_mar">March will be some different type of month. You will be happy will have support from your parents, family and everything. Your partnership will give you good results. Gains from opposite sex will be on higher side. Focus yourself in different type of professional activities for getting good results. In the second half your partners or co-born may oppose you on some different issues.</string>
    <string name="taurus_may">During the complete month you will loose your temper excessively without any reasons. Your partner will be annoyed from you due to your temperament and excessive calculations. You will loose a lot in business. If you are in partnership, reducing the use of electronics and speculating in stock market will give extremely bad results. Working hard with the passion will key to success. Your spouse may hearted due to your temperament.</string>
    <string name="taurus_nov">November month will be very soothing. All your family members will be supportive. Some religious function in family will also expected during the month. Your father may fall ill at the same time your business is going to increase. But you must give father’s health on the priority.</string>
    <string name="taurus_oct">This month is full of action. Professionally you will enjoy full support of family and friends. But difference your father can not be ruled out over the family or religious expenses. Avoid investing in stock market, lottery or gambling. You will be the looser. At the end of month you might face some controversies or problems with your father. Chances of bad reputation can not be ruled out. If you are having some issues of females in family than avoid taking rash decisions. Deal these issues very quietly and patiently</string>
    <string name="taurus_sep">This month is quite unpredictable. You will feel like going everything out of your hand. But at the same time family happiness will keep your hopes high. Your family and professional life both will be average. Avoid expressing everything this might leads to depression, seating with the father for the long term will be give extra ordinary good results. Avoid discussing your expenses with the kids.</string>
    <string name="virgo_apr">In this month something good from the spouse is indicated but the partners will remain irritated. You will feel depressed only problem is the partners. Avoid taking some big decisions with the partners. Otherwise hues business loss is indicated.</string>
    <string name="virgo_aug">In this month expenses will break all records. Your travel, business movements, everything will be at the pick. Children will do good, if they are studying abroad or if you planning to go abroad then take your decisions and fly.</string>
    <string name="virgo_dec">This month will be seesaw for you. Something you will become very romantic and sometime you will loose your temper badly. Emotional stress will not be there but other family members will be calculative. Your father may support your younger ones and heated arguments between your mother and spouse is also indicated in this month. In nutshell for Virgo this is an average year.</string>
    <string name="virgo_feb">This month is also full of irritation. You may take some big wrong decisions that can lead to major problems. The family members of opposite sex may face allegations or disputes. If you are running some business in partnership the partner will remain irritated.</string>
    <string name="virgo_jan">This month is full of irritation and expenses, family arguments will be there. Avoid disputes and odd situations which can lead to some bad results. But on the other hand your kids will perform very well in education as well as in everything.</string>
    <string name="virgo_jul">After the soothing two months you may travel for long. Business stress will be there. Again little presser from spouse site is seen but in all around you will remain happy with the positive approach. You will still the time from busy schedule for the happiness and enjoyments.</string>
    <string name="virgo_jun">This month is good in all aspects in matter of professional and emotional gains everything will be settled for the happiness there are chances you may sacrifice. Religious journeys and religious activities will be the part of month. Due to your won sacrfications you might feel little disturb.</string>
    <string name="virgo_mar">This month is quite dangerous. All decisions will go on wrong track. Relationship with the spouse will be bad. If you are having some disputes with the partners or in marriage that will take bad shape. It is better to avoid taking decisions postpone at least for one month.</string>
    <string name="virgo_may">After the span of four months this period is little soothing and positive result giving. Family environment, personal relationship will be better. All disputes will sort out. Business will also grow. Take care your relations with the younger brother this is the only negative of month.</string>
    <string name="virgo_nov">Do not listen your heart you may be in big problems avoid all types of partnerships, emotional or physical relations with the opposite sex. Try to remain with your family for getting the best results.</string>
    <string name="virgo_oct">If your father is working with you then major losses in business is there. If you in government service then work sincerely some allegations or professional problems might be there. If you are working in medical sector then something wrong will happen that might going to disturb your family affairs. At the same time you will get support of your family and friends for the servable.</string>
    <string name="virgo_sep">In this month your decisions regarding profession may take wrong turn and professional activities have lot of variations. Problems from some government issues might knock your doors. Flowing rice in rice in running water for help you in business matters.</string>
    <string name="january_ap">January 2015</string>
    <string name="febuary_ap">Febuary 2015</string>
    <string name="march_ap">March 2015</string>
    <string name="april_ap">April 2015</string>
    <string name="may_ap">May 2015</string>
    <string name="june_ap">June 2015</string>
    <string name="july_ap">July 2015</string>
    <string name="august_ap">August 2015</string>
    <string name="september_ap">September 2015</string>
    <string name="october_ap">October 2015</string>
    <string name="november_ap">November 2015</string>
    <string name="december_ap">December 2015</string>
    <string name="b1">If you enjoy using</string>
    <string name="b2">please take a moment to rate it. Thanks for your support!</string>
   
    <string name="baby_care">BabyCare</string>
    <string name="name">Enter your name</string>
	 <string name="sex">Enter your sex</string>
     <string name="dob">Enter your Date of Birth</string>
     <string name="tob">Enter your Time of Birth</string>
   
     <string name="city">Enter your city</string>
     <string name="state">Enter your state</string>
     <string name="country">Enter your country</string>
     <string name="mob">Enter your mobile no.</string>
     <string name="e_mail">Enter your e-mail</string>
     <string name="query">Enter your query</string>
     <string name="can_not_be_left_blank_">Can not be left blank!</string>
</resources>